A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14 FA286
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 3
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1941-1943; 1947 (Box 73, Folder 979)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1941-1943; 1947 (Box 73, Folder 980)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1941-1943; 1947 (Box 73, Folder 981)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1941-1943; 1947 (Box 73, Folder 982)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Fellowships (C-H), 1941-1948 (Box 73, Folder 983)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Fellowships (K-W), 1941-1948 (Box 73, Folder 984)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Field Trip Memoranda, 1940-1948 (Box 73, Folder 985)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Field Trip Memoranda, 1940-1948 (Box 73, Folder 986)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Field Trip Memoranda, 1940-1948 (Box 73, Folder 987)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1931-1940 (Box 73, Folder 988)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1931-1940 (Box 73, Folder 989)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1931-1940 (Box 73, Folder 990)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1931-1940 (Box 73, Folder 991)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1931-1940 (Box 73, Folder 992)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 993)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 994)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 995)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 996)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 997)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 998)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 999)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 1000)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 1001)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 1002)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 1003)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1004)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1005)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1006)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1007)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1008)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1009)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1010)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1011)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1012)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1013)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1014)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1015)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1016)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1017)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1018)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1019)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1020)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1021)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1022)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1023)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1024)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1025)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1026)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1027)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1931-1951 (Box 76, Folder 1028)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Medical Education Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1949 (Box 76, Folder 1029)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports, 1943-1947 (Box 77, Folder 1030)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports, 1943-1947 (Box 77, Folder 1031)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports, 1943-1947 (Box 77, Folder 1032)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports, 1943-1947 (Box 77, Folder 1033)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports, 1943-1947 (Box 77, Folder 1034)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports, 1943-1947 (Box 77, Folder 1035)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports, 1943-1947 (Box 77, Folder 1036)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports, 1943-1947 (Box 77, Folder 1037)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports, 1943-1947 (Box 77, Folder 1038)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports, 1943-1947 (Box 77, Folder 1039)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports, 1948-1949 (Box 78, Folder 1040)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports, 1948-1949 (Box 78, Folder 1041)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports - Pre-Opening, 1941-1943 (Box 78, Folder 1042)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Monthly Reports - Pre-Opening, 1941-1943 (Box 78, Folder 1043)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Nursing Education Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 78, Folder 1044)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1947 (Box 78, Folder 1045)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1947 (Box 78, Folder 1046)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Public Health Program - Correspondence, February 8-24, 1944 (Box 78, Folder 1047)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Publicity - Announcements and Brochures, 1943-1945 (Box 78, Folder 1048)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Reports (Box 78, Folder 1049)
    "Central Michigan Community Hospital," - December 6, 1945 "Michigan Hospital Plan,"- November 1948 "Rules and Regulations for Hospitals and Maternity Homes," [Michigan State Welfare Commission] - 1938/1942
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Site Selection Data, 1939-1940 (Box 78, Folder 1050)
  - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1943-1948 (Box 78, Folder 1051)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Accounting Manual Instructions - Correspondence, 1931-1932 (Box 78, Folder 1052)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Audit Reports, 1929; 1947; 1953 (Box 78, Folder 1053)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Contracts, February-April, 1951 (Box 78, Folder 1054)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1942-1951 (Box 78, Folder 1055)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Disbursements, 1925-1941 (Box 78, Folder 1056)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Disbursements, 1925-1941 (Box 78, Folder 1057)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Equipment - Purchase Orders and Work Sheets, 1931-1933 (Box 79, Folder 1058)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Fellowships (A-G), 1929-1941 (Box 79, Folder 1059)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Fellowships (H-M), 1929-1941 (Box 79, Folder 1060)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Fellowships (O-W), 1929-1941 (Box 79, Folder 1061)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Field Trip Memoranda, 1926-1932; 1946-1947 (Box 79, Folder 1062)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Field Trip Memoranda, 1926-1932; 1946-1947 (Box 79, Folder 1063)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Field Trip Memoranda, 1926-1932; 1946-1947 (Box 79, Folder 1064)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1924-1933 (Box 79, Folder 1065)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1924-1933 (Box 79, Folder 1066)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1924-1933 (Box 79, Folder 1067)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1924-1933 (Box 79, Folder 1068)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1924-1933 (Box 79, Folder 1069)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1070)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1071)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1072)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1073)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1074)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1075)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1076)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1077)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1078)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1079)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1928-1951 (Box 80, Folder 1080)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Minutes - Administrative Board and Executive Committee, 1927-1934; June 22, 1940 (Box 80, Folder 1081)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1927-1948 (Box 81, Folder 1082)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1927-1948 (Box 81, Folder 1083)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1927-1948 (Box 81, Folder 1084)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1927-1948 (Box 81, Folder 1085)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1927-1948 (Box 81, Folder 1086)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1927-1948 (Box 81, Folder 1087)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1927-1948 (Box 81, Folder 1088)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1927-1948 (Box 81, Folder 1089)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1927-1948 (Box 81, Folder 1090)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1927-1948 (Box 81, Folder 1091)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Monthly Reports, 1948-1951 (Box 82, Folder 1092)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Nurses' Home Addition - Correspondence Memoranda and Vouchers, 1930-1933 (Box 82, Folder 1093)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1943 (Box 82, Folder 1094)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1934-1946 (Box 82, Folder 1095)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Public Health Program - Correspondence Memoranda and Vouchers, 1931-1932 (Box 82, Folder 1096)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Site Selection Data, 1925 (Box 82, Folder 1097)
  - Murfreesboro, Tennessee - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1930-1948 (Box 82, Folder 1098)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Audit Reports, 1940-1942; January-December, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 1099)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Contracts, 1940-1942 (Box 82, Folder 1100)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Building Requisitions - Change Orders, 1940-1942 (Box 82, Folder 1101)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1940-1943 (Box 82, Folder 1102)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1940-1943 (Box 82, Folder 1103)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1940-1943 (Box 82, Folder 1104)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Disbursements, 1941-1948 (Box 82, Folder 1105)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1940-1942 (Box 83, Folder 1106)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1940-1942 (Box 83, Folder 1107)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Equipment - Requisition Lists, 1941-1942 (Box 83, Folder 1108)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Equipment - Requisition Lists, 1941-1942 (Box 83, Folder 1109)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1940-1942 (Box 83, Folder 1110)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1940-1942 (Box 83, Folder 1111)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1940-1942 (Box 83, Folder 1112)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1940-1942 (Box 83, Folder 1113)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1940-1942 (Box 83, Folder 1114)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1940-1942 (Box 83, Folder 1115)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1940-1942 (Box 83, Folder 1116)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Fellowships (C-R), 1940-1948 (Box 84, Folder 1117)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Field Trip Memoranda, 1939-1948 (Box 84, Folder 1118)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Field Trip Memoranda, 1939-1948 (Box 84, Folder 1119)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Field Trip Memoranda, 1939-1948 (Box 84, Folder 1120)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1940 (Box 84, Folder 1121)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1940 (Box 84, Folder 1122)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1940 (Box 84, Folder 1123)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1940 (Box 84, Folder 1124)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1940 (Box 84, Folder 1125)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1940 (Box 84, Folder 1126)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1940 (Box 84, Folder 1127)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1940 (Box 84, Folder 1128)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1942 (Box 85, Folder 1129)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1942 (Box 85, Folder 1130)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1942 (Box 85, Folder 1131)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1942 (Box 85, Folder 1132)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1942 (Box 85, Folder 1133)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1942 (Box 85, Folder 1134)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1942 (Box 85, Folder 1135)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1942 (Box 85, Folder 1136)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1942 (Box 85, Folder 1137)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1942 (Box 85, Folder 1138)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1940-1942 (Box 85, Folder 1139)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1140)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1141)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1142)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1143)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1144)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1145)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1146)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1147)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1148)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1149)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1150)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1151)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1152)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1938-1951 (Box 86, Folder 1153)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1939-1949 (Box 87, Folder 1154)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1939-1949 (Box 87, Folder 1155)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1939-1949 (Box 87, Folder 1156)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1939-1949 (Box 87, Folder 1157)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Monthly Reports, 1942-1945 (Box 87, Folder 1158)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Monthly Reports, 1942-1945 (Box 87, Folder 1159)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Monthly Reports, 1942-1945 (Box 87, Folder 1160)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Monthly Reports, 1942-1945 (Box 87, Folder 1161)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Monthly Reports, 1942-1945 (Box 87, Folder 1162)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Monthly Reports, 1942-1945 (Box 87, Folder 1163)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Monthly Reports, 1942-1945 (Box 87, Folder 1164)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Monthly Reports, 1946-1949 (Box 88, Folder 1165)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Monthly Reports, 1946-1949 (Box 88, Folder 1166)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Monthly Reports, 1946-1949 (Box 88, Folder 1167)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Monthly Reports, 1946-1949 (Box 88, Folder 1168)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Monthly Reports - Pre-Opening, 1940-1942 (Box 88, Folder 1169)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Nursing Appraisal/Routine, 1944-1945 (Box 88, Folder 1170)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1947 (Box 88, Folder 1171)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Prepayment Plan - Brochures, 1941-1942 (Box 88, Folder 1172)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1941-1945 (Box 88, Folder 1173)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Public Health Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, February-July, 1941 (Box 88, Folder 1174)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Publicity - Brochures and Clippings, 1941-1967 (Box 88, Folder 1175)
  - Pittsfield, Illinois - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1942-1947 (Box 88, Folder 1176)
  - Provo, Utah - Accounting Procedure Manual for the Hospital Service Plan, March 1942 (Box 88, Folder 1177)
  - Provo, Utah - Audit Reports, 1938-1939; January-December 1947 (Box 88, Folder 1178)
  - Provo, Utah - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Contracts, 1938-1941 (Box 88, Folder 1179)
  - Provo, Utah - Building Requisitions - Change Orders, 1938-1950 (Box 88, Folder 1180)
  - Provo, Utah - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1938-1951 (Box 89, Folder 1181)
  - Provo, Utah - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1938-1951 (Box 89, Folder 1182)
  - Provo, Utah - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1938-1951 (Box 89, Folder 1183)
  - Provo, Utah - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1938-1951 (Box 89, Folder 1184)
  - Provo, Utah - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1938-1951 (Box 89, Folder 1185)
  - Provo, Utah - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1938-1951 (Box 89, Folder 1186)
  - Provo, Utah - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1938-1951 (Box 89, Folder 1187)
  - Provo, Utah - Building Requisitions - Purchase Orders, 1939-1940 (Box 89, Folder 1188)
  - Provo, Utah - Disbursements, 1939-1948 (Box 89, Folder 1189)
  - Provo, Utah - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1938-1942 (Box 89, Folder 1190)
  - Provo, Utah - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1938-1942 (Box 89, Folder 1191)
  - Provo, Utah - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1938-1942 (Box 89, Folder 1192)
  - Provo, Utah - Equipment - Requisition Sheets, 1939-1940 (Box 90, Folder 1193)
  - Provo, Utah - Equipment - Requisition Sheets, 1939-1940 (Box 90, Folder 1194)
  - Provo, Utah - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1937-1939; 1947 (Box 90, Folder 1195)
  - Provo, Utah - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1937-1939; 1947 (Box 90, Folder 1196)
  - Provo, Utah - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1937-1939; 1947 (Box 90, Folder 1197)
  - Provo, Utah - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1937-1939; 1947 (Box 90, Folder 1198)
  - Provo, Utah - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1937-1939; 1947 (Box 90, Folder 1199)
  - Provo, Utah - Fellowships (A-F), 1939-1948 (Box 90, Folder 1200)
  - Provo, Utah - Fellowships (G-M), 1939-1948 (Box 90, Folder 1201)
  - Provo, Utah - Fellowships (O-Z), 1939-1948 (Box 90, Folder 1202)
  - Provo, Utah - Field Trip Memoranda, 1937-1946 (Box 90, Folder 1203)
  - Provo, Utah - Field Trip Memoranda, 1937-1946 (Box 90, Folder 1204)
  - Provo, Utah - Field Trip Memoranda, 1937-1946 (Box 90, Folder 1205)
  - Provo, Utah - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1980 (Box 91, Folder 1206)
  - Provo, Utah - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1980 (Box 91, Folder 1207)
  - Provo, Utah - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1980 (Box 91, Folder 1208)
  - Provo, Utah - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1980 (Box 91, Folder 1209)
  - Provo, Utah - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1980 (Box 91, Folder 1210)
  - Provo, Utah - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1980 (Box 91, Folder 1211)
  - Provo, Utah - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1980 (Box 91, Folder 1212)
  - Provo, Utah - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1980 (Box 91, Folder 1213)
  - Provo, Utah - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1980 (Box 91, Folder 1214)
  - Provo, Utah - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1980 (Box 91, Folder 1215)
  - Provo, Utah - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1927-1951 (Box 91, Folder 1216)
  - Provo, Utah - Minutes - Executive Board and Board of Directors, 1938-1949 (Box 92, Folder 1217)
  - Provo, Utah - Minutes - Executive Board and Board of Directors, 1938-1949 (Box 92, Folder 1218)
  - Provo, Utah - Minutes - Executive Board and Board of Directors, 1938-1949 (Box 92, Folder 1219)
  - Provo, Utah - Minutes - Executive Board and Board of Directors, 1938-1949 (Box 92, Folder 1220)
  - Provo, Utah - Monthly Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 92, Folder 1221)